A Guide to the L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
- Worthington, Katherine Stuart Flanagan, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Wray, Elizabeth Watts, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Wray, Joseph Nathaniel, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Wren, Anthony Degg, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Wren, Harriett Rust, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Wren, Thomas J., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Wren, William Hening, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Wrenn, Kate Campbell, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Wrenn, Lewis Orian, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Wrenn, Lillie Faircloth, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Wright, Carrie Briggs, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Wright, Charles Edwin, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Wright, Cora Lee, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Wright, Della Preston, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Wright, Elizabeth Parry, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Wright, Ethel Wells, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Wright, Fannie Rossie, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Wright, George C., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Wright, George Ridgeway, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Wright, George, Jr., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Wright, Gladys C., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Wright, Ida Louise, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Wright, Ina Smith, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Wright, James Jackson, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Wright, James Leitch, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Wright, Jane Wilson, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Wright, John Alexander, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Wright, Kate Elizabeth, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Wright, Loulie Brook, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Wright, Malcolm A., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Wright, Margaret E., 1934 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Wright, Mary Brinkley, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Wright, Mary Louise, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Wright, Mary Neal, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Wright, Melville G., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Wright, Raleigh Lewis, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Wright, Richard B., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Wright, Richard R., 1974 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Wright, Robert Lewis, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Wright, Rosa Bowles, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Wright, Sadie Sydnor, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Wright, Sally Wilson, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Wright, Sarah Sydnor, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Wright, Virginia Pollard, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Wright, Wesley, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Wright, Wilhelmina Frances, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Wyatt, Benjamin Sylvester, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Wyatt, Clifton Fontaine, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Wyatt, Edward B., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Wyatt, Harry Lee, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Wyatt, Nannie E., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Wyatt, Sarah Hamly, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Wyatt, Thornton Jefferson, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Wynne, Catherine D., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Wynne-Roberts, Lionel C., 1984 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Wyse, Joseph H., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Wysor, Ruth Puckett, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Yancey, Alice K., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Yancey, Virginia S., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Yarborough, Francis Louis Farrow, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Yarbrough, Pinkie Agnes, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Yarrington, Roberta Alexander, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Yates, Eugenia Sneed, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Yates, Wilford C., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Yeaman, John David [infant], 1967 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Yeamans, Mollie K., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Yetter, Walter S., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Yonge, Lutie Archer, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Yonts, [infant] son of Painter Thomas, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Youell, Rice M., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Youell, Susan McNutt, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Young, Annie M., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Young, Annie Pleasant Gray, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Young, Armistead Churchill, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Young, Armistead Churchill, Jr., 1986 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Young, Bryan Thomas [infant], 1958 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Young, Charles Arden, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Young, Chesley Gray [infant], 1975 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Young, Claudia Palmer, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Young, Emma Lee Turner, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Young, Florence V., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Young, John, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Young, Julia Moncure, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Young, Lulie Walker, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Young, Myrtle Virginia, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Young, Russell Wesley, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Young, William Henry Palmer (also see oversize), 1981 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Young, William Ormond, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Younger, Helen Tanner, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Zachary, George England, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Zappia family, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Zappia Ruth Margaret H., 1982 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Zappia, Daniel Russell, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Zappia, Karen J., 1982 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Zappia, Samuel Salvatore, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Zimmerly, Frances Vaughan, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Zimmerman, Clifford William, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Zincke, Charles A., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Zincke, Margaret Louise, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Zincke, Mary Elizabeth, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Zollicoffer, Charles Edward, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Zollicoffer, Helen Garnett, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Zollicoffer, Mary G., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Zylstra, Adelaide F. S., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 27)